Jeongwhan Choi

jeongwhan.choi@yonsei.ac.kr Homepage Link Google Scholar Link

Introduction

I am an integrated Ph.D. student advised by Noseong Park in the Dep. of Artificial Intelligence at Yonsei University. I have a broad interest in graph neural networks, recommender systems, spatio-temporal forecasting, and differential equations. Recently, I have been working on developing graph-based deep learning methods inspired by differential equations in natural science.

I was an undergrad at Jeonbuk National University (2016-2020), majoring in *software engineering*. I was privileged to be advised by Suntae Kim and Duksan Ryu.

Research Interest

- Artificial Intelligence
 - Graph Neural Networks
 - Recommender Systems
 - Spatiotemporal Forecasting
 - Neural ODEs/CDEs/RDEs
- Software Engineering (SE)
 - Software Defect Prediction
 - AI based Software Analytics

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Integrated Ph.D Student

Aug 2020 - Now

Biq Data Analytics Lab (BiqDyL), Yonsei University (Advisor: Prof. Noseong Park)

Undergraduate Student Research Assistant

Jan 2020 - Aug 2020

AI & SE Lab, Jeonbuk National University (Advisor: Prof. Duksan Ryu)

Undergraduate Student Research Assistant

Nov 2018 - Nov 2019

SSEL(Software System and Engineering Laboratory), Jeonbuk National University (Advisor: Prof. Suntae Kim)

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Integrated Ph.D, Artificial Intelligence

Sep 2020 - Now

Yonsei University, Seoul, Republic of Korea

Bachelor, Software Engineering

Mar 2016 - Aug 2020

Jeonbuk National University, Jeonju, Jeollabuk Do, Republic of Korea

• magna cum laude (GPA: 3.98/4.50)

PUBLICATION

Jeongwhan Choi, Seoyoung Hong, Noseong Park and Sung-Bae Cho, "GREAD: Graph Reaction-Diffusion Equations," arXiv preprint arXiv: Arxiv-2211.14208, 2022. [pdf from arxiv.org]

Jaehoon Lee, Chan Kim, Gyumin Lee, Haksoo Lim, **Jeongwhan Choi**, Kookjin Lee, Dongeun Lee, Sanghyun Hong and Noseong Park, "Time Series Forecasting with Hypernetworks Generating Parameters in Advance," arXiv preprint arXiv: Arxiv-2211.12034, 2022. [pdf from arxiv.org]

Jeongwhan Choi, Seoyoung Hong, Noseong Park and Sung-Bae Cho, "Perturbation-Recovery Method for Recommendation," arXiv preprint arXiv: Arxiv-2211.09324, 2022. [pdf from arxiv.org]

Hwangyong Choi, **Jeongwhan Choi**, Jeehyun Hwang, Kookjin Lee, Dongeun Lee and Noseong Park, "Climate Modeling with Neural Advection-Diffusion Equation," *Knowledge and Information Systems*, 2022. [IF=3.205]

Seoyoung Hong, Heejoo Shin, **Jeongwhan Choi**, and Noseong Park, "Prediction-based One-shot Dynamic Parking Pricing," In *Proceedings of the 31st ACM International Conference on Information and Knowledge Management (CIKM)*, 2022.[pdf from arxiv.org][GitHub]

Jeongwhan Choi, Hwangyong Choi, Jeehyun Hwang and Noseong Park, "Graph Neural Controlled Differential Equations for Traffic Forecasting," In AAAI, 2022. [pdf from arxiv.org][pdf from AAAI][GitHub][Regular Paper Acceptance rate: 14.2% (1,161/8,198)] [Overall Acceptance rate: 15.2% (1,370/9,020)]

Taeyong Kong, Taeri Kim, Jinsung Jeon, **Jeongwhan Choi**, Yeon-Chang Lee, Noseong Park and Sang-Wook Kim, "Linear, or Non-Linear, That is the Question!," In Proceedings of the 15th ACM International Web Search and Data Mining Conference (WSDM), 2022. [pdf from arxiv.org][GitHub] [Regular Paper Acceptance rate: 15.8% (80/505)] [Overall Acceptance Rate: 18% (315/1,765)]

Jeongwhan Choi and Duksan Ryu, "Self-Supervised Learning Using Feature Subsets of Software Defect Data", In *Proceedings of the Korea Software Congress (KSC)*, Dec. 2021, pp.203-205.

Jeehyun Hwang, **Jeongwhan Choi**, Hwangyong Choi, Kookjin Lee, Dongeun Lee and Noseong Park, "Climate Modeling with Neural Diffusion Equations", In *Proceedings of the 21st IEEE International Conference on Data Mining (ICDM)*, 2021. [pdf from arxiv.org] [GitHub] [Regular paper acceptance rate: 9.9% (98/990)] [Overall Acceptance Rate: 20% (198/990)]

Jeongwhan Choi and Duksan Ryu, "Bayesian Optimization Framework for Improved Cross-Version Defect Prediction", *KIPS Transactions on Software and Data Engineering (KTSDE)*, Vol. 10, No. 9, pp. 339-348, Sep. 2021.

Jeongwhan Choi, Jinsung Jeon, and Noseong Park, "LT-OCF: Learnable-Time ODE-based Collaborative Filtering", In *Proceedings of the 30th ACM International Conference on Information and Knowledge Management (CIKM)*, 2021. [pdf from arxiv.org] [Github] [Regular paper acceptance rate: 21.7% (271/1,251)] [Overall Acceptance rate: 22% (1,101/4,989)]

Jeongwhan Choi and Duksan Ryu, "Bayesian Optimization Framework for Cross-Version Defect Prediction", In *Proceedings of the 23rd Korea Conference on Software Engineering (KCSE 2021)*, 2021, pp. 63-72. [Best Paper]

Jeongwhan Choi, Jiwon Choi, Duksan Ryu and Suntae Kim, "Improved Prediction for Configuration Bug Report Using Text Mining and Dimensionality Reduction," *Journal of KIISE*, 2021, Vol. 48, No. 1, pp. 35-42.

Jeongwhan Choi and Duksan Ryu, "A Study on the Applicability of Transfer Learning Techniques for Cross-Project Defect Regression," In *Proceedings of the Korea Software Congress (KSC)*, 2020, pp. 150 - 152.

Jeongwhan Choi, Duksan Ryu, and Suntae Kim, "Comparative Study of Transfer Learning Models for Cross-Project Automotive Software Defect Prediction," In *Proceedings of the Korea Computer Congress* (*KCC*), 2020, pp. 257–259.

Jeongwhan Choi, Jiwon Choi, Duksan Ryu, and Suntae Kim, "Prediction for Configuration Bug Report Using Text Mining," In *Proceedings of the 22nd Korea Conference on Software Engineering (KCSE 2020)*, 2020, pp. 350–357.

Jeongwhan Choi, Jiwoo Noh, and Suntae Kim, "Prediction Techniques for Difficulty Level of Hanja Using Multiple Linear Regression," *J. Inst. Internet, Broadcast. Commun.*, vol. 19, no. 6, 2019.

Seounghan Song, **Jeongwhan Choi**, Mingu Kang, and Cheoljung Yoo, "A Software Module That Analyzes the Relationship Between Headline and Content of the Web Article: CHIMERA," in *Proceedings of the 2019 KIIT DCS Summer Conference*, 2019, vol. 14, pp. 437–440.

Jeongwhan Choi, "Iceberg-Ship Classification in SAR Images Using Convolutional Neural Network with Transfer Learning," *J. Internet Comput. Serv.*, vol. 19, no. 4, pp. 35–44, 2018.

Innovation Award, Yonsei University (Best paper in Dept. of Artificial Intelligence)

Jul 2021

• Media link

Best Paper Awards in KCSE 2021 in Software Engineering Day

Feb 2021

• Received the best paper award in the 23rd Korea Conference on Software Engineering (KCSE 2021)

Best Awards in Software Engineering Day

Dec 2019

- Software Engineering Day, Dep. of Software Engineering, Jeonbun National University
- A Software Module That Analyzes the Relationship Between Headline and Content of the Web Article: CHIMERA

Best Paper Awards, Korean Institute of Information Technology

Jun 2019

• A Software Module That Analyzes the Relationship Between Headline and Content of the Web Article: CHIMERA

The National Scholarship for Science and Engineering, KOSAF(Korea Student Aid Foundation)

2018-2019

• This scholarship supports undergraduates with strong academic performance in science and engineering, with the purpose of developing future leaders in those fields.

Academic Excellent Scholarship

2016-2019

Jeonbun National University grants a scholarship for the student who has the best grade.

Talks

Talk on 1st Worshop on AI held by Yonsei Univ. [slide link][Poster]	Oct 2022
Poster presentation for AIGS Symposium 2022 held at the COEX Grand Ballroom [Poster]	$Aug\ 2022$
Invited talk on Top-conference session, Korea Computer Congress (KCC 2022) [Slides]	$Jul\ 2022$
Tutorial on Korea Artificial Intelligence Association (KAIA)	Nov 2021

- Topic: "Graph-based Collaborative Filtering and Neural ODEs"
- This talk is part of a tutorial called "Deep Learning Inspired by Differential Equation" [Slides].

SERVICE

- Reviewer in Learning on Graph Conference (LoG) 2022
- Reviewer in IEEE Transactions on Intelligent Transportation Systems in 2022
- External reviewer in ICDM 2021, 2022

PATENT AND S/W PROGRAM

[Issued Patent] Graph Neural Controlled Differential Equations for Traffic Forecasting, Noseong Park, **Jeongwhan Choi**, Jeehyun Hwang, Hwangyong Choi, Domestic Patent(Issued Number: 10-2022-0151819). 2022.11.14

Nov 2022

[S/W] LT-OCF: Learnable-Time ODE-based Collaborative Filtering, Korea Copyright Commission, C-2021-052779, 2021.12.

Dec 2021

[Issued Patent] LT-OCF: Learnable-Time ODE-based Collaborative Filtering, Noseong Park, **Jeongwhan** Choi, Jinsung Jeon, Domestic Patent(Issued Number: 10-2021-0177928). 2021.12.13 Dec 2021

[Granted Patent] Apparatus and Method for Measuring Difficulty Level of Chinese Character Using Regression Analysis, Suntae Kim, **Jeongwhan Choi**, Jiwoo Noh, Domestic Patent(Application Number:10-2019-0141339). 2019.11. [link]

University Machine Learning Camp in Jeju, Jeju University

Aug 2020

• See credential

IBM Blockchain Foundation for Developers, Coursera

Feb 2018 - Present

• License 5MMQUBFWE2K3 (See credential)

Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree, Udacity

Jan 2018 - Present

• See credential

Machine Learning, Coursera

July 2017 - Present

• License EEYYGQPCFLN7 (See credential)

SKILLS

Tools & Technologies,

- PyTorch, TensorFlow, Python
- Java, C/C++, R, LaTeX, VBA, Unified Modeling Language
- Android, Matlab, Git, RSA
- MySQL, Tomcat, JSP, HTML, Javascript, JUnit

Industry Knowledge,

- Artificial Intelligence, Graph Neural Networks, Neural Ordinary Differential Equations (Neural ODEs), Recommender Systems, Time-series Forecasting, Spatio-temporal Forecasting, Software Defect Prediction
- Software Engineering, Object Oriented Programming, Design Pattern, Compiler, Software Testing(Static Analysis)
- Text Mining, Image Processing for SAR Image
- ARM Cortex-M3, ESP-8266

PROJECTS (FROM 2017 TO 2019)

Prediction for Configuration Bug Report Using Text Mining

Nov 2019 - Dec 2019

• The purpose of this project is to predict the configuration bug reports using machine learning techniques and NLP.

Development of capability assessment evaluation algorithm for personalized self-study with Hanja-Chinese parallel $Dec\ 2018\ -\ Expected\ Nov\ 2019$

- The purpose of this project is to solve the problems of existing Hanja character difficulty selection method.
- It includes the technique for measuring the difficulty of Hanja characters using artificial intelligence.
- It also covers personalized learning induction technique using a clustering model.

Stock Price Prediction Model Based LSTM to Maximize Return on Investment

Oct 2018 - Dec 2018

- The purpose of this project is to predict the long-term stock flow based on the AI prediction model and to derive meaningful ROI.
- This project has a paper which is not submitted.
- See project

Advanced Lane Finding Project

Jul 2018

- The goal is to find the lane line using advanced techniques.
- See project

Vehicle Detection Jul 2018

- The Software Pipeline to Detect Vehicles in a Video.
- See project

Clone Driving Behavior

Jun 2018

- The goal is to clone driving behavior via the CNN model.
- See project

Recipe Assistant App

Apr 2018 - Jun 2018

- This project is the recipe assistant app which helps people to cook an easy way.
- See project

Tic-Tac-Toe game for LPC 1768

Jun 2018

- This project is the Tic-Tac-Toe Game using ARM Cortex-M3(LPC 1768)
- See project

Lane Finding Project

Mar 2018

- The goal is to find the lane lines on the road.
- See project

Iceberg Classifier

Jan 2018

- The goal is to create an image classification model that finds icebergs among SAR images collected by satellites.
- This project has a paper published in JICS.
- See project

Helicopter Battle Game

Apr 2017 - Jul 2017

- This project is the game improvement project in Java.
- See project

Smart Mailbox

Sep 2017 - Dec 2017

- This project is the smart mailbox notifies a user when a new mail arrives at the mailbox.
- See project